------------------ED-----------------------------
樱律联萌站 http://bbs.ylbud.com/
樱律联萌站为您带来高质量中日双语字幕
In the great sea of Ignora lay
five islands in the shape of a cross.
大海いうぬら浮かぶ一際は広い中央の対中中心都市
中日双语字幕由 樱律字幕组 制作
感谢以下成员倾情制作
听译：五月、吉禾　校对：jez　时间轴：咲夜　后期：OMG
Four pointed in each cardinal direction
around a larger one in the center
東西南北の大陸を十字架に見立てって
to form Ente Isla, the islands
watched over by the gods.
神々の見守るの島エンテイスラ
All who lived in Ente Isla
knew of Satan, ruler of demons.
魔王サタンを知らぬ物など
このエンテイスラの地にはいない
His very name was synonymous
with the terror and cruelty
それは闇の生き物が
蠢く魔界を統べる
which ruled this demon realm
teeming with creatures of the night.
恐怖と残酷の代名詞
Satan's ambition was to conquer the human world
魔王サタン人間世界を支配し
and build there a land of peace and
prosperity for all night's creatures.
すべての闇物達の王道楽土建設する野望に抱く
He had four trusted generals:
魔王サタンには腹心の四天王はあり
Adramelech, Lucifer, Alciel, and Malacoda.
アトラメレク
ルシフェル
アルシエル
マラコータ
These four great demons launched
attacks on the four continents.
四人の悪魔大元帥
四つの大陸を攻める
However, a lone hero rose up
against them, sacred sword in hand.
だがそこに
一人の勇者が聖剣を手に立ち上がる
Along with a band of comrades, the hero
crushed Lucifer's army to the west.
勇者、仲間達とともに西のルシフェル軍を殲滅する
They went on to defeat Adramelech in
the north and Malacoda in the south,
さらに北のアトラメレク
南のマラコータを倒し
and then the federation
of knights led by this hero
勇者の人にした連合国騎士団
invaded the central continent, where
the lord of demons kept his castle.
中央大陸に境参る
魔王城に攻めに
Damn! You wretched humans!
可恶 区区人类！
Divine souls, gather in the realm of the dead.
Stop the demons and drag them to the netherworld!
召集世间的圣灵之魂
停止时间吧 下坠黄泉！
What?!
什么？
How dare you!
可恶
Sire!
魔王大人
Out of my way!
可恶　　　　　滚开
I am sorry, Sire.
实在抱歉 魔王大人
The human forces are
steadily overcoming my army.
现在人类的军队在慢慢压制我军
It is only a matter of time
before this castle falls.
这个魔王城的陷落也只是时间问题了
I never dreamed a single human "hero"
勇者也只不过是个人类
could force us into such dire straits...
居然能追到这里来
Sire,
魔王大人
I suggest we withdraw for
now and regroup.
现在先撤退吧 再重来一次
人类们！
Hear me, humans!
今日暂且
I shall leave Ente Isla in your hands today!
将安特伊苏拉让与你们
But know this: I shall return
但是我必定会
to subjugate you and all of Ente Isla!
在你们手中将安特伊苏拉夺回来的
The Devil Arrives in Sasazuka
魔王、笹冢に立つ
Where are we?!
这里是？
魔王大人
-Are you all right, Sire?
您没事吧
Alciel, the first thing we must
do is find a place to heal.
艾尔西尔噢
首先必须找到可以治愈伤口的地方
Yes, Sire.
可是
But this seems an awfully noisy place...
这好像是个很吵的地方
Wh-What is this world?!
啊　什么 这个世界是？
Could it...
魔王大人 您的模样
Sire?! Why do you take that form?!
What?
怎么会
These are...
这个是
...human hands?
人类的手
Calm yourself, Alciel.
冷静点 艾尔西尔
We must be careful not to use magic.
不要轻易使用魔法
Excuse me, you there!
あの、そこのお二人さん
Could I talk to you for a minute?
ちょっとだけ時間いいかな
Do not speak to me so familiarly, lowly human!
你们
区区人类
Do you wish to die?
想要死吗
Uh-oh, they're foreigners.
外人さんですよ
Okay, do you boys understand Japanese?
お兄さん達日本語分かる？
You look injured. Were you in a fight?
ケガするみたいだけど
喧嘩でもしたかも
为什么呢
Why?! Even if they do not speak our language,
就算语言不通
I am a demon, a user of magic...
也不会认不出带有魔力的恶魔
Alciel.
艾尔西尔
现在别使用魔力
Do not use your magic now.
Not until we learn of this world.
在对这个世界还不了解之前
Aren't they hot, dressed like that?
しかし、その格好熱くないのかね
They're "cosplaying," Sir. Don't see
that much in this neighborhood, though.
あれっすよ、cosplayっすよ
この辺じゃあまり見ないっすけどね
This is Sasaki on patrol duty. I've got
some boys with minor injuries here.
辺野リの佐々木です
軽度傷害事件発生の模様
This seems to be a carriage...
这好像是马车的样子啊
The victims are foreigners
from somewhere in Asia.
We're in west Shinjuku, area 1-20.
But it doesn't require horses...
但又不需要马
Not sure whether they're tourists or residents.
好像也不是用魔力来作
It doesn't seem to be powered by magic...
为动力吧
Now, can I get you to join us
in the car? If nothing's wrong...
では、ちょっと乗ってもらえるかな
何もなければ
区区人类
Do not presume to touch me, lowly human!
别轻易地碰我！
Know your place, you inferior creature!
应该知道你的身份 下等生物！
Okay, you two behave yourselves.
じゃ、大人しくしててね
Um, this is katsudon, okay?
This isカツ丼 OK?
Katsu... don...
カツどん
Yes, yes.
yes yes
They coated animal flesh in some
sort of grain and fried it in hot oil.
獣の肉に穀類をわどわす
高温の油に浸した物
Then they put a mashed-up bird egg on top,
鳥類の卵ぐちゃぐちゃにして
それを上にかけ
and heated it even further in a fish broth...
魚汁思ってさらに加熱したもの
I'm not actually supposed to feed you,
まあ、本当はこういうのダメなんだけどね
but you two are injured,
so we'll just call it my treat.
あんたら被害者し
僕のおごりことって
我想要知道关于这个世界更多的情报
I want more information about this world.
What? Oh, yes.
はい
回答我的问题！
Answer my questions.
艾尔西尔
Alciel.
艾尔西尔？
Alciel?
魔王大人
Satan!
H-Hey, you can't just come in here!
ちょっとダメだよ
勝手に入ちゃ
住嘴
Silence.
Y-Yes, Sir...
はい
魔王大人
King Satan...
原来您没有事啊
I'm so glad you're all right.
总之
I used hypnotism to gain some
information about this world...
我使用了催眠术
得到了这个世界的情报
Apparently we've come to a world called "Earth."
ここは地球という世界らしい
We're in one of its nations,
an archipelago called "Japan."
その内の国の一つ
日本という島国だ
We stand now in its capital of "Tokyo,"
その首都にあたるのが今
この地である
東京であり
and this building is someplace
called a "police station."
この建物は警察署という場所のようだ
The police are evidently a state
institution which maintains public order.
警察は社会の実状を守る
国家機構の一つらしい
なるほど
I see. And what is that substance on the table?
では　そのテーブルの上の物
"Katsu Doon." It's an extremely
common food in this country.
カツどん
この国にある
極一般的な料理だ
"Katsu Doon"...
カツどん
Yes, that has a powerful ring to it.
This is of great interest.
なるほど
力強い響きだ
興味深い
What? N-No, it's not particularly important.
いや、これはそれほど重要な物ではない
In this world, things like spell-casting,
magic, demons, and the Devil
この世界では魔法や魔力
魔王や悪魔と言った存在はすべて空想上の物であり
are considered fantasies...
things that don't really exist.
実在しないとされているのだ
Magic doesn't exist?! How could that be?!
魔力が存在しない
そんなバカな
I see, so the insufficient magic here
なるほど
では魔力不足のせいで
left us unable to retain our demonic forms?
我々は悪魔の姿も保たなくなったですね
Yes. But who would have thought we'd
look like this stripped of our magic...
しかし
それは剥げをした姿はこれと
案外人間と言う物はすべて生き物の根幹を成しているかもしれんな
Perhaps humans actually form
the basis of all living creatures.
You jest, Sire.
I'm sure it's merely an effect
of this world and the Gate.
恐らく
この世界やゲート作用による物でしょう
I still retain some of my magic.
俺はまた若干な魔力を残している
It's quite an effort to stem
its outward flow, though.
流れてる止めるはなかなか骨だかな
What about you, Alciel?
お前はどうだ
アルシエル
King Satan, is this?
魔王様　これは
No, I highly doubt you conjured this with magic.
多分魔力による作用ではあるまい
Oh.
なるほど
If I adjust the amount of magic
I release, I won't run out for a while.
魔力は放出量を調整すれば
すぐこーカツすることはない
The real problem is that we
have no way to amass more.
問題は再び蓄える手段はないということだ
Still, if Earth is familiar with the
concept of magic, even as "imaginary,"
だが架空とはいえ
魔力は魔法の概念はあるなら
there may be some method
of recovering our powers.
魔力を回復する手段があるかもしれん
The path left to us is to discover
that method and get them back.
俺達の残された道はその手段を見つけ
魔力を回復させること
Until then, we have no choice
それまでは
この人間達のルールを従い
but to live in this world
and obey these humans' rules.
その世界で生きていくしかない
What a cruel reality this is.
なんという過酷な現実だ
うん、そのためにはまず
Yes. Our first step is...
この区役所で戸籍と住民表を手にいる
...to obtain "records" and "certificates
of residence" at this "ward office."
魔王大人
Sire...
H-Hmm?
はい
Here.
"Sadao Maou"
"Head of Household"
All right. Next, we create accounts at the "bank."
次は銀行に口座を作る
To do so, we use this.
それにはこれをつく
What is that paper?
その紙は
It's this country's currency.
この国の通貨だ
あの警察の人間から拝借した
I borrowed it from that police person.
We also need a seal.
I whipped one up for myself.
そしてそのはんこうを使う
さっき適度につくった
Most impressive.
さすが
"Lifelong Safe Trust"
"Super Fixed Deposit"
Here you are.
どうぞ
Good. Now we just need to secure
a base of operations from a "real-tore."
Realtor
残るは不動産屋で活動拠点を手にいれる
We are searching house!
俺達、家が探してられます
What sort of home do you have in mind, Sir?
どんな条件の物件を探し
He understood you!
能够沟通了！
冷 冷静点 艾尔西尔
C-Calm down, Alciel!
学习这点程度的语言而已
A little language acquisition is nothing for me!
小菜一碟
好 好的
O-Okay! I'm in the groove here!
跟上节奏了
The landlady here is a very admirable person.
こちらの大家さんは
非常に奇特な方でして
If I may speak frankly,
she says she wants to set an example
はっきり申しあげて
お客様のような身元ふたしたの方を
by taking on persons of
unknown background, like you.
祖先して引き受けてしたているんです
这 这是
Th-This is...
啊啊 我居然也明白了
Yes. Even I can tell...
不对  可是
Well, at least it's a two-story house...
不管怎么说 还有二楼
房间也有六个
And it has six rooms.
You'd be renting room 201 here.
この二○一の室になります
这有这一间吗
We get one room?
我觉得这也就比外面强点
I suppose we should be grateful it has a roof...
和之前的魔王城相比
Certainly when you compare it
to the Devil's Castle, it's a bit...
稍微有点…
ご機嫌よ
Good afternoon.
这是人吗
Is it... human?
貴方々が今回入居希望されるお二人ですね
You two are the new rental applicants, correct?
居然说话了
It spoke?!
This is the apartment owner. She lives next door.
こちらアパートとなりにするんしゃる大家さんです
志葉美輝です
I am Miki Shiba.
美輝は美しい輝くとかきます
That's "Miki" spelled with the
kanji for "beauty" and "radiance."
Oh, but do feel free to call me "Mikitty."
でも　気軽にミーキーティー
と呼んで下さって結構ですのよ
是
Right...
Sire, are you sure this is the right place for us?
魔王様　本当にここでよかったのですか
It seems that in this world
they say "patience is a virtue."
この世界には臥薪嘗胆という言葉があるらしい
This style of Devil's Castle
will make a nice change.
このような魔王城はまた一強だ
Oh, Sire...
魔王様
ここから新しい一歩を踏み出そうでは
From here, we shall take
a new step... for... ward...
ま....いいか
King Satan! King Satan!
魔王様！
King Satan!
魔王様！！
Central Police
Hospital
I didn't realize this body required food!
まさかこの体　食事が必要だったと
It is a human body, Sire.
人間のからだですからね
Not to mention that "IV drip" thing
cost a full month's rent on the castle!
しかもあの点滴といれ　一回分で
魔王城一月の家賃と同等だと
You know what they call that here?
"Rubbing salt into a wound"!
これをなき面にはちと
この国ではいうらしいぞ
Sire, that uncanny landlady
spared us a good deal of trouble.
しかしあの永代のシュレナいようやの助けがなければ
危ないところでした
She tells me that Japan requires
residents to carry health ins...
聞くところによると
国民健康保険...
Anyway! Money is clearly of
the essence in this human society.
とにかく
この人間社会ではお金こそが必要不可欠なのだ
I can't afford to expend any
more of my magic, either.
此れ以上魔力も消費できん...
Which means we have only one choice left.
となれば残された手段はたった一つ
What is that, Sire?
それは一体？
Whoops, I did it wrong.
あっ　間違えた
馬鹿野郎　履歴書なんてただじゃネイだぞ
You idiot! Résumé forms
don't grow on trees, you know!
Okay, I'm "Sadao Maou"...
よし　真奥貞夫と
"Shiro Ashiya" ...Do you think
this name is strange, Sire?
アシアシロ　この名前　変じゃないですかね
It's too late to ask me that!
We already made IDs!
いまさら言うな
もう戸籍作っちゃうだから
King Satan.
魔王様
Yeah?
ああ？
Might I suggest you put a little
more thought into your spending?
もう少し計画的にお金を使われてはいかがですか？
I'm thinking plenty!
Summer's coming, so we need a fridge,
十分計画的だろう
夏を前に　冷蔵庫は必要だし
and owning a laundry machine is
cheaper than coin laundry in the long run.
洗濯機も長期的に見れば
コインランドリーより安くすく
The bike is essential for commuting to work.
自転車はバイトの日々に必須だ
That's not the issue, Sire!
そういうことを言ってるのではありません
分割払いといってもあったのではないかと言うことです
I'm questioning why you
didn't pay in installments.
I hate loans.
俺ローンってキライだ
Now look here...
あのですね
And installment plans come with fees, you know!
大体分割払いは手数料かかるだろう
I ain't paying for something
I can't touch with my own hands!
俺実体のないものにお金払いたくない
ではお聞きしますよ　魔王様
In that case, let me ask you this:
How are we supposed to make it to payday
on milk, konjac jelly, and cucumbers?!
こんにゃくときゅうりと牛乳で
どうやって次の給料日までく食いつくなんておつもりですか？！
Well...
うわ～別に一文無しになったわけじゃないし
It's not like we've got no money left!
I've still got some in my wallet!
財布にはまだ～お金が残ってるし
それにほら
And hey, they give me meals at work!
バイト先の間がないとか
We'll die.
死にますよ
これから給料日まで
You propose we eat burgers and fries
three times a day until payday?!
毎日ハンバーガーとポテトオンリですから
What is this, Super Size Me?
スーパーサイズ二位ですか
You plan to eat a high-calorie,
high-cholesterol diet from a young age?
わが一日ハイプレＸＸＸＸ十分楽しいですねＸＸＸＸＸＸ
I look forward to ten years from now!
I just hope you don't die prematurely of a
lifestyle-related illness before we get home!
I must apologize for my cowardice, Sire,
but you're the one who
argued for biding our time!
You of all people ought to prize constant
diligence and health maintenance!
Put a sock in it! I'm going to work!
うるせい！バイトの時間だ
Wait, Sire!
魔王様！
説教は帰ってから
Lecture me later!
No, I mean you forgot your umbrella!
違います　傘傘
Let's go, Dullahan!
いくぞはんこ
さて　私も出かける準備をしますか
Well, I suppose I'll get ready too.
Here.
あのう　これ
Please, use this.
よかったら使って
えーと　あのう
Er, um...
I work right nearby.
At the MgRonald's by the train station.
俺　バイト先すぐそばだから
駅前のマグロナルド
じゃ
All right...
I don't even care if you throw it out!
それすいちゃてもいいから
う～～つめてい～～
Yeesh, that's cold!
This week is key! It decides who sells the
most of our feature item in our district!
今週はキャンべン商品の地区売り上げ
一位がかかった大事な一週間
I swear, I will break the sales
record for black pepper fries!
必ずやブラックペッパーポテトの売り上げ
ベストを更新してやる
いらっしゃいませ
Welcome to MgRonald's. May I take your order?
ご注文はお決まりですか
A cheeseburger and a small cola.
チーズバーガーとコーラのエスサイズ
May I interest you in some black pepper fries?
They're our featured item.
ご一緒にただいまキャンべン期間中の
ブラックペッパーポテトもいかがですか
No, thanks.
いや　いいです
- Yes, these little continuous efforts are necessary
- One cheeseburger and one small cola...
そう　こういう小さな積み重ねが
- for my eventual comeback as lord of demons!
- that will be 220 yen.
いつかまおうとして復活するために必要なのだ
- for my eventual comeback as lord of demons!
- Here's 1,000.
Let me get your change.
千円お預かりします
That's one chicken burger, one
iced coffee, and one Happiness Meal.
チキンバーガーとアイスコーヒー
ハピネスセットで
730 yen, please!
七百三十円になります
あ　後もしよろしければ
Oh, would you like to use
our microwave, Ma'am?
電子レンジお使いになられますか
あ？/え？
If you've brought baby food
that can go in the microwave,
レンジで調理できる離乳食でお持ちであれば
I'll heat it up while you wait.
お一緒に暖めますけれど
あ。。。
You're sure you wouldn't mind?
じゃあ　お願いできますか
My pleasure, Ma'am.
かしこまりました
Mr. Maou, you're really amazing!
やっぱり真奥さんすごいですね
赤ちゃんの離乳食のことにも気づくなんて
I can't believe you thought
of her baby food, even!
Oh, that.
ああ　さっきの
Accommodating our customers'
needs when we have the time
時間のあるときは
やっぱお客さんのニーズにおおした柔軟な対応が
長期的にはプラスになるんだよ
gives us a long-term advantage.
You're so cool! You're like a real working adult!
なんかかっこいいです
社会人って感じで
Er, well, it is only a part-time job...
まあ　バイト　だけどね
Central
Library
Another job lost, Ashiya.
あ....また職を失ったぞ　アシア
アルシェールと呼びください
Please call me "Alciel," Sire.
Anyway, our goal is to return
to Ente Isla, not to do day labor!
そもそも　俺らの目的はエンテーイスラに戻ることであって
日銭を稼ぐことないぞ
As you say, Sire.
まあ　おしゃること通りですが
You find us a way to get back our magic.
お前は魔力を取り戻す手段を探したぜ
Sire?
は？
I'll work and earn us money. You use your brains.
俺が働いて金を稼ぐ
お前は頭を使え
This world knows the concepts
of magic and spell-casting.
この世界にも魔王や魔力という概念があるんだ
Maybe if we trace them to their source...
その元を探し出せば　いいわ
You believe we'll be able to recover our powers?!
魔力を回復手段もあると
Yes. And then we won't stop at Ente Isla.
ああ～魔力を取り戻した暁には
エンテーイスラだけじゃない
I say we rule this world, too!
この世界も支配してやろうじゃないか
Sire!
魔王様
You mean "Maou."
真奥だ
As you wish, Sire. I, Alciel, vow to
discover the path to your supremacy!
かしこまりました
このアルシェール
魔王様のハートへの道
必ず探し出して見せます
Rise, Alciel. You're embarrassing me.
おい　立てアルシェール
恥ずかしいだろう
Utopias of
the World
And yet...
て言ったのに
おい！時給２００円あるだぞ
Hey! I got a 100-yen-per-hour raise!
Listen, the guy who started today is pretty good!
今日会った新人
なかなか優秀でさ
Reference Book Use Only
No Private Studying
You're at the bottom of the totem pole, Sire!
完全にしたっぽありませんが魔王様
If the Devil is an underling,
what does that make me?!
魔王様はしたっぽなら
私は一体どうだってしまうですか
はあ。。。
Not that I've made progress on this front either...
じゃ言ったまま
こっちに進展あるわけでもないし
Peru's Nazca Lines
Egypt's Pyramids
England's Stonehenge
And with only books to go on,
all I can do is speculate...
本だけじゃ推測することしかできないしなあ
Oh, an earthquake.
あ。。＝＝
地震だ
真奥さん　地震です
Mr. Maou, it's an earthquake.
Yes, yes it is.
うん　そうだね
Hey, Chi.
ちいちゃん
Yes?
はいTT？
誰にだってミスはある
Everyone makes mistakes.
But it's the sixth time I've dropped
fries on the floor this month!
だって今月六度目なんですよ
ポテトゆかにばらないただの
True, you do drop them every other day.
そうだね
二日は一度は巻いてるね
I just clean up after myself while
everybody else waits on customers...
みんなは接着をしているとき掃除してる私って
At this rate potatoes will
start sprouting from the floor!
このままじゃ四日から追いままはいちゃいます
おい　休憩中の若人たち
Hey, you kids on break.
What's wrong, Chi?
どうしたちいちゃん
どうしたんです？店長
What's wrong, Manager?
Call me "Miss Kisaki"!
木崎と呼びなさい
It's getting crowded out there.
そろそろ込み始めた
休憩終わったら振るかとしてくれ
When your breaks are up,
I want you operating at full power.
キャンべン一位にはここからは勝負だ
This is when the fight for #1 really gets in gear.
I'm counting on you.
頼むぞ
後それから芋巻はほどほどにしとけよ　さっさき
Oh, and try not to plant
too many potatoes, Sasaki.
Yes, Ma'am.
はい
- One MgBurger meal with black pepper fries!
- One order of large black pepper fries, please!
マグロバーガーのセット/ブラックペッパーポテト
Welcome to MgRonald's.
いらっしゃいませ
A smile, please!
スマイルください
い、いらっしゃいませ
W-Welcome to MgRonald's...
If we keep this up, we can do it!
We can make #1 in the district!
こうペースなら行ける
地区売り上げ一位取れる
あっ？
They're not done yet?
まだ上がってない
Don't tell me the fryer's broken?!
まさか故障？！
ブラックペッパーだけに故障？！
Did it have to be the black pepper fryer?!
何ていってる場合じゃない
Okay, Maou, focus! What now?
どうする
If I don't do something,
making #1 is the least of our problems!
このままじゃキャンペン一位どこらか
Do I use my magic?
使うか
残された魔力
Please save your magic for emergencies, Sire.
魔力はいざというときのために
残しておいてください
What's wrong?
どうした？
えっ？
Life is fail.
終わった
It's not your fault, Mr. Maou.
真奥さんのせいじゃないんですし
And the repairman should be done by evening!
夜には修理間に合うみたいですし
Hey, Maa, got a second?
真奥君　ちょっといい？
Yeah.
はい
What's going on? Is she gonna
blame me for us not getting #1?
なんなんだ急に
もし一位は達成ならずの責任を取らされるとか
No, it's not like I broke it...
あいや
あれは俺が壊したわけじゃないし
Or does she suspect me because
I was about to use magic?!
まさかさっき魔力を使おうとしたことがあやし舞ってるか
Thanks for waiting! Here we go.
お待たせ
まあ楽にしなさい
At ease, kid. It's not bad news.
悪い話じゃないよ
I just got the approval from the district office.
先管轄事業所から認可の連絡はあってね
Uh, what?
あっは...
Sadao Maou, as of today,
I'm promoting you to A-level staff.
真奥貞夫
本日よりA級クルーに昇進だ
All right!
さ～～！！
I'm A-level staff, Ashiya! I got a raise!
A級クルーだぞあしは
級アップだ
Hey.
ね
Huh? Oh, it's you.
今朝の
あの後　あなたの店に行ったわ
I went to your restaurant after we spoke.
Oh, you did? I didn't see you.
You should've said something!
あ？そうなんだ
気づかなかったよ
声かけてくれればよかったのに
I watched you all day from
the bookstore across the street.
絶対のかんや本屋から観察してたの
あ？
You look so different that
I thought I was mistaken, but...
外見があまりにも違うし
勘違いガだったと思うけど
You started to cast a spell.
魔力を使おうとしたでしょう
A spell?
魔力って
Wait, are you...?!
お前！
まさか
Why exactly are you working
part-time at MgRonald's, Satan?!
何であなたはマグロナルドでバイトをしてるの
魔王サタン
Emilia the hero?!
勇者エミリア
一二三四
Where will morning start from, in this quiet sky?
どこから朝になる
从何处开始是清晨
静かな空
安静的天空
Fingertips twining in a pinky
swear I pretended not to see
見ないふりをした指きり
装作没看见的拉钩
恋日の先笑われた
恋爱之前被嘲笑
If the moon's been laughed at,
she'll sink away toward yesterday
つきなら  消えてゆくんだ
就算是月亮 也会要消失
昨日の方角
向着昨天的方向
Liar, coward... if I'm all these things at once
うそつき　臆病者
胆小的人　说谎精
みんなまとめて　  僕なら　最低言ったのは
大家总结的这些　　我的话   就说声差劲
Then I only blossomed in dreams
夢の中だ
在梦中
I hid in the moon's shadow,
but the truth is, I was crying
月の影に隠してた
藏在月影中
本当はね　泣いていだ
其实正在哭泣
The tears won't flow anymore...
did they all dry up?
涙はもう流れない
眼泪已经不再流
枯れてしまうたな
枯竭了吧
If I could forgive everything,
maybe they'd flow again
何もかも許せたら
虽然什么都原谅的话
流れるかもしれないけど
眼泪可能还是会流出来
But these are all things I want to protect
守りたいものばかりだなあ
全都是想要守护的东西
The Hero Stays at the Devil's Castle for Work Reasons